<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NaiTour</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nairobi_night_photo">Nairobi Night Photo</string>
    <string name="nairobi_kenya">Nairobi, Kenya</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">East Africa\'s most cosmopolitan city, Nairobi is Kenyas beating  heart, an exciting, maddening concrete jungle that jarringly counterpoints the untrammelled natural beauty to be found elsewhere in the country</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="tag_line">Nairobi\'s Pocket Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="nairobi_image">Nairobi Image</string>
    <string name="kenya">Kenya</string>
    <string name="nairobi">Nairobi</string>
    <string name="the_city_reaching_for_the_skies">The city reaching for the skies</string>
    <string name="aboutA">Nairobi\'s polarising character ensures that the city is reviled and loved in equal measure, and even those who love it might well admit that it is  the kind of place many rave about only once they\'re away from it. For those who call it home, the city\'s charms include a vibrant cultural life, fabolous place to eat and exciting nightlife. Its detractors point to its horrendoud traffic, poor safety levels (\'Nairoberry\' is a common expat nickname) and its less-than - gorgeous appearance.</string>
    <string name="aboutB">However, with a fabolous national park on its doorstep, some wildlife-centric attractions, the excellent National Museum and a series of quirky sights, Nairobi\'s reality - like that of so many places with a bad reputation - will often come as a pleasant suprise</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="top_experiences">Top Experiences</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="facts_about_nairobi">Facts About Nairobi</string>
    <string name="nairobi_history_body">Nairobi began in the late 1890s as a railway camp, where the British rested as they built the \'lunatic express\' - the Mombasa to Uganda railway line. It was originally named \'Ewaso Nai´beri\', but the British had difficulty pronouncing this and, instead, coined their own name \'Nairobi\'. Because of its central location in Kenya, Nairobi later became the British provincial capital and, finally, the capital city of Kenya</string>
    <string name="nairobi_history">1. Nairobi History</string>
    <string name="get_there_body">If you are flying to Kenya, Nairobi is the perfect starting point for traveling to the various areas of the country. It\'s centrally located, with an international airport and converging road network connecting it to most parts of Kenya. International airlines fly to Nairobi from Europe, the United States, Asia, the Middle East, Australia and other places. Nairobi is also the main airline hub to most other African countries and destinations. The main railway line also passes through Nairobi, and there are plenty of private and public transportation options for traveling between Nairobi and other Kenyan cities.</string>
    <string name="get_there">2. How to get there</string>


</resources>
